MΑT BUSCH

CONTACT

0413810616



mathewbusch2@gmail.com



mathewbusch.com ==



EDUCATION

University of Sydney **Design Computing** 2015 - 2018

SKILLS

Design

UX/UI design

Interaction design

Design thinker

Sketch, Figma, Studio

Adobe CC & MC

InVision

Development

HTML, CSS, JS

React, Angular jQuery, Bootstrap

React Native

API's including Google Maps

ABOUT ME

I am a easy going light hearted guy who enjoys the challenge of taking complex user flows and turning them into simple user experiences through use of data.

I come from a strong broadcast and media centric background having worked on TV shows to media products and now in house at Suncorp, helping to personalise the customers journey thorugh their range of Insurance and Banking products. I love a coffee or a cheeky beerafter work too.

EXPERIENCE

Wunderman Bienalto 2018 - Present

Delivery Lead Optimisation Team

Hands on designing and developing new expereinces for financial and Insurance institutions on both the website and application spaces through the use of data and customer insights.

VPA Technologies (Ligr Systems) Jan 2015 - Feb 2018 Head of Design and Development

UX design and creation of an in house graphics engine product used to automate graphics for sporting bodies like Cricket Australia, Athletics Australia and Football NSW.

REFRENCES

Tikali Nicholls - Visit Victoria (0413975335)

Adam Burke - LIGR Systems CTO (0402430658)

Dr Caitilin de Berigny - University Of Sydney (+61 2 93515933) or (caitilin.deberigny@sydney.edu.au)